<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FloridaCrackr</title>
    <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FloridaCrackr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 15:21:15 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://drewgriffin.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      
        <description>DrewGriffin.com is a personal blog made using the wordpress platform and studiopress framework.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, DrewGriffin.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. DrewGriffin.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how DrewGriffin.com’s visitors use its website.
DrewGriffin.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jack E. Griffin</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/dad/</guid>
      
        <description>Remembering Dad When I was 20 years old, my granddad (we called him Papa) passed away. He was 92 years old. He was the father of seven and had been married 62 years until my Grandma Griffin had passed two years prior. My dad, Jack, was the youngest of the Griffin kids. During the graveside service, it seemed like there were well over one hundred people in attendance. I knew most of the onlookers because the family get-togethers were a gracious plenty to use a grandma phrase and with six sets of aunts and uncles and all of my first cousins.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma Ivey</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/grandma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/grandma/</guid>
      
        <description>Grandma Ivey Chantel’s and my grandmother passed away last night. While sad, this life was a stepping stone and she is now with the Lord.
While on this earth, she instilled in me such pride. She was born in Tampa in March 1917. While most families may have a couple generations in this area, my grandmother wasn’t even the first Tampa native. Her mother, Edna Miley, was born in the Dade City hotel in 1884.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/about/</guid>
      
        <description>I was born in the old St. Joseph Hospital in Tampa, FL. I am a fourth generation Tampa native and very proud of that fact.
I am 50 years old now. I have the great fortune to own the title of “dad”. To me, it is without question the greatest thing I have done in my life.
On January 30, 2010, DeeDee Brinkman and I were married in a small, but elegant gathering of friends and family.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Wedding</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/wedding/</guid>
      
        <description>DeeDee and I decided long ago that a traditional wedding was not the approach we wanted to take. We both agreed that Chantel and Mike’s (my sister and her husband) wedding was more to our liking.
Chantel and Mike got married at Circles Bistro in South Tampa. A friend married them. The food was excellent and the cake was from Wright’s Gourmet in South Tampa.
Like Chantel and Mike, we decided to check out some restaurants that we enjoy including Gino’s, Tio Pepe in Clearwater, the Columbia Restaurant in Ybor and a few others.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BBQ Sauce</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/bbq-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/bbq-sauce/</guid>
      
        <description>Barbecue Sauce As you know, I love BBQ. Here is a sauce recipe. The simple sauce is for my friends and family who do not enjoy heat while partaking in some delicious BBQ. The Spicier sauce is more for the ladies and gents that like a little more kick to their BBQ experience. Simple Sauce
1 1/2 cups of ketchup 1 cup of apple cider vinegar 1/4 cup of Worcestershire sauce 1/4 cup of soy sauce 1 cup of packed dark brown sugar 2 Tablespoons of chili powder 2 cloves of minced garlic 2 Tablespoons of vegetable oil 3 slices of oranges NOTE: I use a sauce pan, put the first two ingredients (ketchup and cider vinegar) and then put the pan on low while I add and mix the rest of the ingredients.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange Dream Pie</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/orange-dream-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/orange-dream-pie/</guid>
      
        <description>Orange Dream Pie INGREDIENTS 1 8-ounce package of Pepperidge Farm Chessmen Butter Cookies 1/4 cup butter or margarine, melted 1 8-ounce package cream cheese, softened 1/3 cup powdered sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 1 12-ounce container frozen whipped topping, thawed and divided 1 1/4 or so cups of orange curd (see recipe below) 2 teaspoons grated orange rind 2 tablespoons fresh orange juice INSTRUCTIONS
Stir together cookie crumbs and butter; press evenly in bottom and up sides of a 9-inch pieplate.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pound Cake</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/poundcake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/poundcake/</guid>
      
        <description>Mom’s Pound Cake INGREDIENTS
3 cups all-purpose flour 3 cups sugar 5 eggs 3 sticks butter (or margarine) 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp pure vanilla extract 1 tsp lemon extract 1 cup milk DIRECTIONS
Mix wet ingredients Mix in sugar Gradually mix in flour Bake at 325 degrees for one hour or until done. Notes: I would use a greased tube pan for this.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>