<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>food on FloridaCrackr</title>
    <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in food on FloridaCrackr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://drewgriffin.github.io/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BBQ Sauce</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/bbq-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/bbq-sauce/</guid>
      
        <description>Barbecue Sauce As you know, I love BBQ. Here is a sauce recipe. The simple sauce is for my friends and family who do not enjoy heat while partaking in some delicious BBQ. The Spicier sauce is more for the ladies and gents that like a little more kick to their BBQ experience. Simple Sauce
1 1/2 cups of ketchup 1 cup of apple cider vinegar 1/4 cup of Worcestershire sauce 1/4 cup of soy sauce 1 cup of packed dark brown sugar 2 Tablespoons of chili powder 2 cloves of minced garlic 2 Tablespoons of vegetable oil 3 slices of oranges NOTE: I use a sauce pan, put the first two ingredients (ketchup and cider vinegar) and then put the pan on low while I add and mix the rest of the ingredients.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Orange Dream Pie</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/orange-dream-pie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/orange-dream-pie/</guid>
      
        <description>Orange Dream Pie INGREDIENTS 1 8-ounce package of Pepperidge Farm Chessmen Butter Cookies 1/4 cup butter or margarine, melted 1 8-ounce package cream cheese, softened 1/3 cup powdered sugar 1 teaspoon vanilla extract 1 12-ounce container frozen whipped topping, thawed and divided 1 1/4 or so cups of orange curd (see recipe below) 2 teaspoons grated orange rind 2 tablespoons fresh orange juice INSTRUCTIONS
Stir together cookie crumbs and butter; press evenly in bottom and up sides of a 9-inch pieplate.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pound Cake</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/poundcake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/poundcake/</guid>
      
        <description>Mom’s Pound Cake INGREDIENTS
3 cups all-purpose flour 3 cups sugar 5 eggs 3 sticks butter (or margarine) 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp pure vanilla extract 1 tsp lemon extract 1 cup milk DIRECTIONS
Mix wet ingredients Mix in sugar Gradually mix in flour Bake at 325 degrees for one hour or until done. Notes: I would use a greased tube pan for this.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>