<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>family on FloridaCrackr</title>
    <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in family on FloridaCrackr</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 15:21:15 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://drewgriffin.github.io/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jack E. Griffin</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/dad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/dad/</guid>
      
        <description>Remembering Dad When I was 20 years old, my granddad (we called him Papa) passed away. He was 92 years old. He was the father of seven and had been married 62 years until my Grandma Griffin had passed two years prior. My dad, Jack, was the youngest of the Griffin kids. During the graveside service, it seemed like there were well over one hundred people in attendance. I knew most of the onlookers because the family get-togethers were a gracious plenty to use a grandma phrase and with six sets of aunts and uncles and all of my first cousins.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grandma Ivey</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/grandma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/grandma/</guid>
      
        <description>Grandma Ivey Chantel’s and my grandmother passed away last night. While sad, this life was a stepping stone and she is now with the Lord.
While on this earth, she instilled in me such pride. She was born in Tampa in March 1917. While most families may have a couple generations in this area, my grandmother wasn’t even the first Tampa native. Her mother, Edna Miley, was born in the Dade City hotel in 1884.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Wedding</title>
      <link>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/wedding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2010 15:21:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://drewgriffin.github.io/posts/wedding/</guid>
      
        <description>DeeDee and I decided long ago that a traditional wedding was not the approach we wanted to take. We both agreed that Chantel and Mike’s (my sister and her husband) wedding was more to our liking.
Chantel and Mike got married at Circles Bistro in South Tampa. A friend married them. The food was excellent and the cake was from Wright’s Gourmet in South Tampa.
Like Chantel and Mike, we decided to check out some restaurants that we enjoy including Gino’s, Tio Pepe in Clearwater, the Columbia Restaurant in Ybor and a few others.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>